[
{	
	"front": "... is the capital of Georgia?",
	"back": "Atlanta"
},

{
	"front": "... is the capital of Pennsylvania?",
	"back": "Harrisburg"
},

{
	"front": "... is the capital of California?",
	"back": "Sacramento"
},

{
	"front": "... is the capital of Alaska?",
	"back": "Juneau"
},

{
	"front": "... is the capital of Tennesse",
	"back": "Memphis"
},

{
	"front": "... is the capital of Alabama?",
	"back": "Montgomery"
},

{
	"front": "... is the capital of Arizona?",
	"back": "Phoenix"
},

{
	"front": "... is the capital of Arkansas?",
	"back": "Little Rock"
},
{
	"front": "... is the capital of Colorado?",
	"back": "Denver"
},
{
	"front": "... is the capital of Delaware?",
	"back": "Dover"
}


]